Hello friends, my name is Ashwini Kumar.
As friends, you already know me.
Friends, I am
working in HDFC Bank.  The topic of today's video is going to be here, you must have already
seen it in the title and thumbnail.  Friends, the
topic of today's video is going to be
about Kotak Mahindra Bank.
Brother, if you want to work in Kotak Mahindra Bank.
Friends, you want to become a Deputy Manager
from Kotak Mahindra Bank and brother, you are
from any state, like you are from Bihar, you are
from Jharkhand, brother, you are from any state,
if brother, you want to do a job
in Kotak Mahindra Bank, that too friends, here as a
Deputy Manager, then friends, today's
video is going to be special for you.
Friends, I am telling you this especially
because brother, the location here
is available for you in Jharkhand and Bihar at present.  But brother, for that
you will have to do one thing here.
Friends, in today's video I am going to
tell you the complete details about how
you can apply for this here, friends,
even the children of Bihar and Jharkhand.
Well friends, it is
available for every state at present
but what happens is that no vacancy etc. is available
in any bank for Bihar and Jharkhand.
As I just told you friends,
for Bihar and Jharkhand, friends, it is going to be here.
What happens is that no
vacancy etc. comes there.  So friends,
this video is going to be special for you.
Friends, in today's
video, I am going to tell you step by step the complete details about
how you
can apply for it here.  And
brother friends, how can you get a job here?  Is
his trick here
going to be?  I am going to tell you the complete information step by
step in today's video.
For this, friends,
you have to do only one thing.  If you like the video, please give it
a like.  If you
are new to the channel then you
must subscribe to the channel.  Because
friends, you keep getting such content here.
Without wasting any time let's
start the video.  Friends, in today's
video we are talking about Kotak
Mahindra Bank.
Brother, if you want to get the post of Deputy Manager in Kotak Mahindra Bank.
Friends, you
want to become a deputy manager here and brother, you
want to secure your future here.  If you
want to make your career in the banking sector, then friends, this video is going to be special for you.
As
I just told you why it is going to be special
?  Because you are eligible for this,
students of Bihar and Jharkhand and brother,
how are you eligible for this, I am going to tell you here
within 1 minute.
Before that friends, let me tell you the update.
Here's the update guys.  As you
know, friends, we run a 14-day
online training program.   In
which, friends, at present,
more than 30 students have already
enrolled here.  If you are
interested, you are from Bihar, Jharkhand, any
state and you want to work
in the corporate office of HDFC Bank, you
want to do a single job without sales and without feed,
then this training program can be
special for you.
You will easily find the link in Discord.  Go
check it out friends.  There I have
explained in full detail
on the website that brother, what all you have to do here
, how to enroll in it.
Only friends, you can
get a job within Rs 5000.  If you want it brother, then
quickly go and check it out.  And
friends, if you have
not joined our WhatsApp group yet, then go
quickly and join the WhatsApp group.
There you keep getting new updates
, new hirings.
Brother, you are going to get a lot of benefits from that.
Friends, without wasting time, I
come back to the topic here and let me tell you in detail about
Kotak Mahindra Bank.
As you already know, in Kotak Mahindra Bank,
you
cannot become a Deputy Manager directly.  As I have already
told you here a long time ago in the video here.  If brother, you
want to become a Deputy Manager, then brother, there
is a course for it here, which friends, ITM
University conducts here.
Friends, if you
want to work in Kotak Mahindra Bank, no matter which
state you are from, there is no issue.
But brother, you have to do one thing here.
If brother, you are from Bihar and Jharkhand then
brother, you will have to relocate here.
You can relocate here within
any of these three cities - Delhi, NCR, Gurgaon or Noida.  No matter
where you are from, it is
not an issue.  So friends, you
can become deputy manager here.  In this, brother,
your salary package is also going to be
quite good here.
Friends, your package here is going to be ₹5 lakh.
And friends, let's talk about age, brother,
if your age is between 21 to 28, if you are
from any state, there is no issue, then
brother, you become eligible here.
And friends, let us talk about
how you have to apply in this?
Friends, let me tell you the process of applying here.
Friends, applying is simple in this,
you
can also visit the website of ITM University here.  Or friends,
you can directly visit the website of Manipal Academy
here.
Or friends, you can also connect with us.
You will easily find the WhatsApp number here
in the description box.
Friends, you
can go and share your resume here.
Friends, what
can we help you with in this?  Brother, are
you facing any problem in your assessment or are you
facing any problem in Intermediate?  If any
issue arises, brother, you can connect with us.
These friends, there is going to be a
program here.  The
program lasts for one year.
Friends, you have to go to ITM University and train here for four months.
You get an internship here for 2 months.
And brother, you get six months of
on-the-job training here.   In
which brother, stipend is also being
provided to you here.
Like you are going to get ₹5,000 here for four months.
After that, brother,
you will get ₹1 or ₹100 here for 2 months,
which will be a stipend.  And
after that, brother, here you are going to get a stipend ranging from ₹24,000 to
₹00
under on the job training.
Friends, here I am talking about Kotak
Mahindra Bank.  Brother, there is going to be a very good
program here friends.
Friends, the name of the program that is going to be there here is going to be
Kotak Next Year Program.  Ok?
As you might have heard in many videos
that Kotak's next year
program is going to be
a very good program in itself, friends.
And brother, here the target and
pressure are also very less compared to
HDFC Bank, ICIC Bank, HD Axis Bank and many more
programs that we run here.
As you know, there are many programs here like HDFC's
Future Bank program, ICICI's, ICIC
Aspire or ICICI's Direct
Sales Manager or Axis's Young
Bank program.
So
friends, in comparison to them, the program that is going to be here is
also the best here on
Kotak Mahindra Bank.  Ok?
Brothers, if you want to work in Kotak Mahindra Bank, then
friends, you
can become a Deputy Manager.  The package is going to be directly ₹5 lakh.  Let's
talk about the
program fee, friends, the program fee is ₹2,37,000 plus
GST.
And friends, this fee which is
going to be yours, friends, you can get an
education loan here.  That means you
can easily join here now free of
cost.  After that brother, you don't have to do anything here.
What happens here your friends
?  Education loan is taken.
What happens in education loan is that the payment you have to make here,
for example, you have paid
₹2,37,000 plus GST, which becomes
₹2,80,000.  If you
take a loan here, brother, what happens to you after that
?  In this, brother,
you have to pay here after 1 1/2 years.  In
which brother, what happens to you here is that
after 1 1/2 years, your EM which
comes to your salary is deducted from your salary.
Ok?  So brother, right now
you do not have to pay anything here.
Just what do you have to do?
You have to join directly and undergo training.
And brother, your stipend
etc. will keep coming here.  Ok?  And friends,
as soon as your salary starts coming,
as soon as you go inside the bank here, then
friends, finally
your
salary will start getting deducted here.  Rest of the
friends, if
you also want to do a job in Kotak Mahindra Bank, then friends, the
best opportunity is going to be there for you here.
As I have told
you the complete process here step by step
as to
how you have to apply here.  What kind of things are going to
live here?
I have told you the complete details here.  I
hope you liked this information in today's video.  If you liked the
video, please give it
a like.  Friends, if
you have not yet subscribed to this channel, then
brother, go quickly and subscribe to this channel.
See you
in the next video.  Take care.  Bye.